Hello everyone! This is Kanami from Tsuchiya, aka Kanami!
Yes, that's right.
Today, I'm going to make with the publicity staff
visit in the very special Hall Tour 2023.
10 grooming locations in Japan
Recommendations for souvenir sightseeing spots~!
Yay!
Yes, that's right, today is the 9th place! Ladies and gentlemen.
It's getting close to the end, but today is the 9th place! Aichi Prefecture!
On Sunday, September 3, we will be performing at Forest Hall, Nihon Tokushu Tokyo Shimin Kaikan in Aichi.
I've asked for your recommendation of Aichi Prefecture for the promotional text on Instagram before the show.
I would like to tell you about it!
So, without further ado, let's get started!
Let's start with gourmet food.
Let's start with gourmet food!
The first one is Hitsujimabushi, which is delicious, and I really enjoy eating it every time I go there.
The first one is Hitsujimabushi, which is delicious, and I really enjoy eating it every time.
I guess it's here.
We often eat Hitsujimabushi here. It's delicious!
And Unafuji.
And Unafuji has Hitsumabushi with liver!
It's very tasty with a lot of liver on top of the hittsumabushi!
The next most popular dish was Miso Katsu (pork cutlet).
This restaurant is said to be the birthplace of Miso Katsu!
Miso Katsu at Yabaton
Waraji Tonkatsu
Teppan tonkatsu with the best ribs!
This restaurant was highly recommended!
Spaghetti with starchy sauce
Miso Stewed Udon Noodles
Misen's Taiwanese ramen
Sugakiya, and many other gourmet restaurants!
Many of them we have eaten before!
We've been to Nagoya for a long time, so we already have a certain amount of familiarity with the city.I've been visiting Nagoya for quite a while now, so I've probably already had some of the famous ones.
I think I've already had some of the famous ones, like the sweet ogula matcha spa at Kista Mountain.
It's famous for its flashy menu.
I heard it's famous. I think I've had it before.
I think I've heard about it before.
I think I heard about it on the radio.
I wonder what it tastes like.
I wonder what it tastes like. I'm a little scared but I want to try it.
The 3rd line of the Sumiyoshi Kishimen Conventional Line offers freshly deep-fried tempura!
Conval's
Shrimp sandwich, miso katsu sandwich, take out, good!
Miso Katsu Sandwich or something delicious Toyohashi Curry Udon Udon noodles with yam and rice under it.
Toyohashi Curry Udon has a different feature from regular Curry Udon, which is that there is rice and yam at the bottom of the bowl of Curry Udon.
Curry udon tends to leave some of the roux behind as you eat the udon.
The idea was born from the thoughtful consideration that the roux tends to remain after the udon is eaten, so that the udon can be enjoyed until the very end.
I've been to countless restaurants in Japan, but I'm still a little curious about them.
I want to try the Nagoya Cochin Oyakodon!
Torigai Sohonke's Nagoya-Kochi oyakodon pudding.
Nagoya-Kochi is also very famous.
Oyakodon is delicious!
I had Nagoya-Kochi oyakodon in Tokyo a long time ago.
And Miso Oden at Goribei!
Looks delicious!
I want to eat Yakitori (grilled chicken)!
I want to eat it!
In Nagoya
Morning at Esker's underground shopping mall!
The famous morning untoast!
It's delicious, isn't it?
It seems that Nagoya is famous for morning cafes.
There are many morning cafes in Nagoya.
Yes, like this!
Next, some souvenirs!
Here you go!
Here you go!Here you go.
The most popular one with three was Piolin.
I've had peorin dozens and dozens of times.
They are so cute!
I heard that the Piolin Challenge is very popular.
Piolin is a pudding, so if you move it around too much, it will fall apart.
I bought it in Nagoya and brought it home.
If you buy it in Nagoya, you can try it and see if you can bring it back home without it falling apart.
If you buy one, please give it a try!
And right now, they have a lemon flavor for a limited time only!
And then the chicken wings!
We got a lot of these two from Sekai no Yamachan Freibo!
Please compare which one is your favorite and let me know!
Aoyagi: The Souhou family's frog buns.
When you open the box, they all look at you with a smile, it's so cute!
Dipped in miso, dipped in miso, akafuku!
It's delicious!
And...
Kakubouzan Kichiimo.
Fireworks!
It's so thin and crispy!
I want to buy it!
I want to eat it so bad!
I'll definitely buy it when I find it!
And Kuririn's Mont Blanc!
It looks so good!
Oh my God, there's so much bathing!
This is so delicious!
And then we go to a tourist attraction!
Atsuta Jingu Shrine, a shrine with deep ties to Oda Nobunaga.
It's the most powerful power spot in Nagoya.
I love power spots!
And the Nagoya City Science Museum is huge and has a lot of exhibits!
It's got the biggest planetarium in the country.
What? I want to see the planetarium!
Sounds fun!Looks so nice and fun!
Port of Nagoya Aquarium Dolphin Show
Sounds fun!
Uryeonomori Forest
It's a nice place where you can walk from Nagoya station!
It's beautiful!
It's beautiful.
Take a look.
I want to go to Ghibli Park. Me too.
What?
And...
Oasis 21. The glass-walled facility.
The lights are beautiful in winter.
I recommend the rooftop.
It's like a view of Nagoya.
It looks like "Nagoya".
Hey, a doll of Nanachan
Oh, there is a doll of Nanachan.
At the station, you can see the different clothes she wears at different times
I picked up various collaborations and things I'm interested in.
I picked up the ones that I think are interesting, but there are so many more, so if there is something else that you are interested in, please search for it.
If there is something else you are interested in, please search for it.
If you can't make it to the Nagoya concert, please enjoy sightseeing and eating delicious food in Nagoya.
If you can't make it to the Nagoya concert, please take it as a reference when you go to Nagoya for your private time.
So, thank you all for watching until the end.
See you soon. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.